hotels.uk.com 2019-07-18

# 

## Privacy & Cookie Policy

This privacy policy sets out how Queensborough Group uses and protects any information that you give to us when you use this website.

We are committed to treating your personal information responsibly and ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

#### What we collect

It is necessary for us to hold and process certain personal information about you in order to enable us to process your accommodation booking. This may include the following information:

  * Name
  * Telephone number
  * Home Address
  * Credit card details for payment purposes.
  * Information relating to your preferences and interests.
  * Names of any guests travelling with you
  * Other information, at your discretion, relevant to customer surveys and/or offers.

#### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Our own internal record keeping.
  * We will need to pass on information you have given us to the Accommodation Providers directly or if they use Booking.com to provide us with rates and availability in order that they can provide the products and services you wish to book.
  * We may use your information for the purposes of providing you with our services and customer care. Our Accommodation providers may use your details for credit checking and debt collection.
  * We may need to disclose your information to public authorities, if requested by them or required by law.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided, if you have agreed to receive this information.

#### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

#### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. The file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer requirements.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website or making bookings.

#### Controlling your personal information

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write or email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information by contacting us here https://www.queensboroughgroup.co.uk/contact/
